{
    "id": "2fd31413fe584eb69cacaffd4951a104",
    "title": "Elder, Eldest, Older, Oldest",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am visiting my …………….. sister tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5550b3fb4d774a0888d51161dbb9d414"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie is five years ………………… than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "264be83e937b49099ae124cc3c7d87ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "My …………………. brother is a pilot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c3bf3d5e6e6e4162baf775efa9821fdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have two .....................… sisters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "92e9c974dcf747f1b7f905e3d7977ce2"
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………………. son works abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c79c655a138f404e8683ddc6ce44ce15"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother is the ..................... member of my family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "454b8324e8144c43b988aa3a8badb5e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the …………………. student in her class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "oldest",
                "eldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cdb45219fc1e4592927bc5a71d3f2ad4"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ..................... son is a journalist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "02ce2cc0983d413f8fe792e8f4f200b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the ………………….. in the family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17996b71747f42a1a4ada1c2a0e9521b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a couple of years ……………….. than him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "Either could be used here",
                "older"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "84ccc3ce313742f89105775e8ef18dcc"
        }
    ]
}